onpointcu.com 2015-04-25

# FACTS

                                      NOTICE OF PRIVACY POLICY
                                WHAT DOES ONPOINT COMMUNITY CREDIT UNION DO WITH YOUR
FACTS                           PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                            Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                                consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you
                                how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice
                                carefully to understand what we do.
What?                           The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service
                                you have with us. This information can include:
                                      Social Security number and income
                                      Account balances and transaction history
                                      Credit history and credit scores
                                When you are no longer our member, we continue to share your information as described in
                                this notice.
How?                            All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
                                business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their
                                customers’ personal information, the reasons OnPoint Community Credit Union chooses to
                                share, and whether you can limit this sharing.
                                                                        Does OnPoint Community           Can you limit this
Reasons we can share your personal information
                                                                          Credit Union share?                sharing?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain your
                                                                                  Yes                           No
account(s), respond to court orders and legal
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes—
                                                                                  Yes                           No
to offer our products and services to you
For joint marketing with other financial companies                                Yes                           No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                                  Yes                           No
information about your transactions and experiences
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
                                                                                   No                     We don’t share
information about your creditworthiness
For our affiliates to market to you                                                No                     We don’t share
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                                 No                     We don’t share
Questions?                       Call us at 503.228.7077 or toll-free at 800.527.3932, or visit www.onpointcu.com.

Page 2                                                                                                           1/13
  Who we are
  Who is providing this notice?          OnPoint Community Credit Union; OnPoint Service Group, LLC
  What we do
  How does OnPoint Community Credit      To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and
  Union protect my personal information? use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These
                                         measures include computer safeguards and secured files and
                                         buildings. We also restrict access to nonpublic personal information
                                         about you to those employees and volunteers who need to know
                                         the information to provide products or services to you.
  How does OnPoint Community Credit      We collect your personal information, for example, when you:
  Union collect my personal information?     open an account or apply for a loan
                                             use your credit or debit card or pay your bills
                                             make deposits to or withdrawals from your accounts
                                         We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                         bureaus, affiliates or other companies.
  Why can’t I limit all sharing?         Federal law gives you the right to limit only:
                                             sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information
                                              about your creditworthiness
                                             affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                             sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
                                         State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to
                                         limit sharing.
  Definitions
  Affiliates                             Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                         financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                             OnPoint Service Group, LLC, a provider of financial services
  Nonaffiliates                          Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                         financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                             OnPoint Community Credit Union does not share with nonaffiliates
                                              so they can market to you
  Joint marketing                        A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that,
                                         together, market financial products or services to you.
                                             Our joint marketing partners include investment and financial service
                                              providers and insurance companies
